what if i told you that you don't have
to worry for future medical expenses
when you suffer from critical illnesses
such as heart attack cancer stroke and
others
the best part is that even if this
illnesses recur there will still be long
some cash provided for you plus a
continuous income stream to help you
recover
good morning everyone i am lester reyes
an agency manager in fwd live
philippines today i'm very very excited
to share with you the newest critical
insurance plan we call
fwd vibrant
fwd vibrant is our complete health
protection from wellness to recovery
so it provides extensive critical
illness protection benefits
from screening
treatment and recovery
so samana avid fans and fwd we already
have critical illness insurance no we
have gunmen our most affordable one for
as low as 1799
it can cover you to 100 000
a lump sum cash for one year
plus 30 000 kovid insurance
we also have set for health
critical illness claim plan
na
that can cover you until age 75 plus a
money-back guarantee
no
and your partner numbing plan is what we
call uh health bundle young health
bundle man incorporates
investment
and critical illness insurance into one
plan
and it can
be added with several protection
benefits catalan hospital confinement
benefit
term
and a lot more
for today
i'm very excited
to say an fwd vibrant
is an enhancement of our set for health
plan because it does not only provide us
multi critical illness claim
but it also provides screaming and
recovery benefits
so isa is
features and benefits
fwd vibrant by skimming through the
pages of
our plan
so i hope you're as excited as i am
let's start reviewing fwd vibrance
product proposition
okay so it in first page nathan
so let me read here
the first few texts of the plan
take control of your health and
well-being from wellness to recovery so
you can pursue your life goals with less
worries
for this proposal
um an acting client is mrs juan de la
cruz
thank you for considering fwd vibrant
critical illness plan
we at fwd understand that you are in
that stage in your life
where you aim for bigger and better
things for you and your family
but in your quest to pursue your goals
you often forget about maintaining good
health
so we designed a product that helped you
take control of your health and
well-being from wellness to recovery
so you're covered before anything
happens right up to after everything
happens
with this sales illustration we will
show the benefits you will receive it
will also explain that are what are
covered and what are not
so gonna
explicitly adding uh introduction for
the proposal
and here you can also observe that the
sales illustration
is prepared for the next 90 days now
from april 15 until
july 13 2022.
fwd vibrant critical illness plan gives
you extensive benefits from screening to
treatment to recovery so you can better
take care of your health and well-being
before anything happens right
up to after everything happens
there's a first page i know
aloha
screening treatment and recovery and
what makes it different from other
critical insurance plans there is in the
market so eternal
overview of the benefits
so here nakalagai is critical illness
protection until age 100
so currently is a
roster before vibrant came in
what we have is critical illness
insurance up to age 75.
no so a lot of people now are clamoring
for protection for critical illnesses
until age 100.
fwd by plan
but on top of the multiple critical
illness claim name is set for health
in our plan dito survived you can claim
up to six times major critical illness
benefits
here you will get 100
of the some assured if in short is
diagnosed with late stage cancer
or a covered non-cancer major critical
illness
so detoxing
[Music]
about cancer remissions or cancer
recurring
instances
so with this plan
is that you don't have to worry for any
future
medical expenses coming from that same
cancer or other cancers
because vibrant will again provide you
100 benefit
to prepare you for for those medical
expenses
apart from that
if unclassified
illness
which again has um
a greater chance of being
[Music]
recurrence after the first one
and of course
there are 42 major critical illnesses
going basis for for claims
you can see the list in section major
critical illnesses you're covered for
parasalis
you can claim up to three times for late
stage cancer
and three times for non-cancer illnesses
one cannot claim more than once for the
same
non-cancer illness
let's say
[Music]
one cannot claim more than once for the
same
non-cancer illness
is heart attack and stroke wherein you
can claim up to three times
multiple critical illnesses
despite the number of
improvements
named when it comes to medical
treatments
sad to say that not everyone
can
easily access that
[Music]
when that happens to us
so you knew first benefit
okay
so
um
critical illness benefits
a vibrant is unlike critical illness
insurance in the market today
critical illness the minor nation you
get 25
of the sun
assured
up to a maximum of one million pesos
if insured is diagnosed with a hovered
minor critical illness
to help with the treatments
so
daddy casey nose set for health and
adding minor critical illness claim
is only 20
of the sum assured
now so let's say 1 million pesos adding
some assured macaroni and critical
mineral no minor critical illness
you get 200 000 before we set for health
however with vibrant pinas
up to 25 percent now so from 200 000
from one million young adding some
assured before
mcgee 250 000
because of vibrant
so we can also see
the minor critical illnesses covered in
this proposal
and you can only
take advantage of this benefit once
but you are still eligible to receive
your other benefits
so again
is on top of
the face amount no
so if ever namakaran and subsequent
major critical illnesses
some assured
at the same time
this plan
uh will give you your been a beneficiary
with 100 of the sum assured
if the insured dies before the age of
however
this benefit will end
once there is a first major critical
illness claim
[Music]
from the plan despite the expiration of
the death benefit
okay
so apart from that we also have what we
call recovery support it
gonna feature an implantation with fwd
vibrant because
it provides health supplement benefit
you will get two percent of the sum
assured for six
consecutive months
upon the first major critical illness
claim to help with medical expenses
so let's say in a corona
critical illness
is a major critical illness claim so
in that way
in that i don't know event okay
however
that is
[Music]
of the sum assured is
i think twenty thousand pesos
so beginning one million pesos the first
major critical illness
twenty thousand a month for the next 6
months
on top dawns of first
next is we have what we call
waving of future payments
is
and with fwd vibrate once in the garage
first critical illness
a new future
[Music]
number one
you become disabled before reaching the
age of 16.
again this is a good feature because
they say bank plans they're in the
market no name is a market
60 years old
waiver of premium so in fwd vibrant
predatory premiums
before reaching the age of 70.
we live in future premiums
[Music]
for the next nine years
another piece of uh mind that
from the plan
apart from that
wellness and longevity benefits
screening benefit
in fwd it matters
we
take care of our health as much as
possible
and what we did is that for us to be
encouraged a laggy time at pacheco
young health screening benefit provides
us with 0.2
of some assured
on the second
the fourth six eight and ten policy
anniversaries
as long as there is no major critical
illness claim yet
no this will help us in monitoring
health and well-being
uh
dear audience
for us to
pay for the checkups that we need to do
to know we're in tip-top shape
so you know since i've been
maturity benefit so another new feature
of our health insurance planner
because
you will get 100
of the sum assured
if insured reaches the age of 100
and has not claimed for any major
critical illness
again the plan
is here for us
to gain peace of mind though just in
case a macaron tyrone and critical
illnesses along the way along our
journey of reaching the age of
retirement
however
again this plan will still reward you
with one hundred percent of the sum
assured
so let's say one one million
in a plan
until age 100
we began
pesos to reward you for staying healthy
until the age of 100.
however
so first major illness
again
benefit
no but then again either
what happened
either mccarran time and saket or hindi
time
might be big
benefit higher than what we paid for
all right
next
so you can next page that in and this
actually summarizes the supplementary
benefits of the plan
because fwd vibrant unlike our set for
health you can add several
riders
in this plan
so for the purpose of this presentation
i only added hospital confinement
benefit i know by hospital confinement
benefit
what we call uh
this is what we call recovery pro
no you'll get 1000 pesos for each day of
confinement in a hospital due to
sickness or injuries
hospital guys nasa philippines
hospital
1000 pesos per day
for
the next 1 000 days
public hosting hospitals
fwd to get additional cash again the
purpose of this hospital confinement
benefit is to complement commercial time
additional medical expenses
can be covered or in these mapat you
adding critical illness insurance
or this will all also provide
for the medical expense for the expenses
of your family
hospital
though
papagalintayo
for at least 1 000 per day
however
if the carotid confinement
uh icu in one thousand pesos per day
energy gain 2000 for each day capac nasa
icu
up to a limit of 365 days
okay
this benefit can only be claimed for a
total of 1000 days before the age of
seventy-five
so in
ito
let's say on the first year nakara
no hospitalization for whatever reason
critical illness related
illness for you to take
advantage of this benefit
let's say 30 days time as a hospital on
the first year no
so 1000 days
baba wasan shannon 30 days so 970 days
and then 30 days time as hospital times
1 000 days
30 000 pesos
from the plan
in 970 these days
from the time that you uh
get the plan
until the age of 75 meron came parent
prepaid number of days
acclaim
but we also get this chance of
recovering from an illness
and get some advantage or benefit from
the plan india
critical illness
okay
so let's go on to another the next page
how this plan works oh let's say one
is a high-powered executive at a
conglomerate so telegon
while already is quite successful he
still has a lot of goals to achieve
with this business schedule taking care
of his health often takes a back seat
on the long scenario
and why
the plan really provides greater value
out of all the insurance plans critical
insurance plans in the market so let's
start with the left side now
so let's say c1 lives to age 98 with
just a minor critical illness diagnosis
okay
so the simulation plan of
today
the following year
so one receives 0.2
of the sum assured
on the second fourth
sixth eighth and ten years so five
five times can be begin every other year
starting the second year
however
[Music]
one receives 25
of the sum assured
upon diagnosis of early stage cancer
so afternoon claiming 25 percent of the
sum assured let's say one million
shannon
and
a minor critical illness claim
250 000 pesos
however after that relational minor
illness
has a one-time long-term
either after macarons and a minor
illness benefit or up until before the
age of 100.
one million pesos
because
here in this example
uh
1.25 million
minor illness
age 100
all right
so economic second scenario what if
something happens and one gets diagnosed
with major critical illness
he is still protected
fwd's got his back so like there's a
first scenario meron parenchang held
screening benefit
five benefits no all throughout the ten
years
and then
nakara
[Music]
which is covered in adding major
critical illness
one hundred percent of the sum assured
so let's say one million is one million
on top of that
supplement benefits
of the sum assured so
20 000 pesos
uh
every month for the next six months
right after the major critical illness
claim
so from 20 000 pesos times six no
one million so two million pesos
20 000 per month for the next six months
so that's one hundred twenty thousand
and then the current passion and two
hundred fifty thousand because bhagavad
gita
health screening benefit no
and then
um 250 so around 2 million 370 000 plus
some health screening benefits
it guarantees you peace of mind
for whatever critical illness or even
disabilities come in our way as we
achieve our goals in life now let's go
on to the proposal details now after
learning all the benefits of fwd vibrant
let's now scrutinize how much it will
cost us to
take advantage of this benefit
so for this example we have fwd vibrant
critical illness plan where in the sum
assured we set it at the lowest which is
500 000 pesos per claim
and since your client nathan is
30 years old
the coverage period is 7 years
no
so 30 plus 70 so for a total of 100
years
so the policy owner is mrs juan de la
cruz
female
she's born in march 15 1992 and she is
also the insured
the issue age is also her current age
which is 30 years old
i and
so you saw my shoulder for the claims
for the major critical illness claim we
have 100 of the some assured like what i
said earlier three times
for the late stage cancer
and another three times for
non-cancer illnesses
so 500 000 per client for a total of six
claims
during the lifetime of the insured
so 500 thousand times six alibaba worst
comes towards talagang the maximize
claims to disappoint
she will get a total of three million
pesos from
fwd vibrant
next issue minor critical illness which
provides additional 25
of the sum assured
so
since 500 thousand adding example 25
of that is 125 000
that is also valid for
the next 70 years until my 100 years old
see
mrs juan de la cruz
next is
benefit or maturity benefit which is
also equal to 100 of the sum assured
if there was no
a major critical illness claim
this will be the death benefit
uh upon death of the insured or the
maturity benefit if the client reaches
the age of 100
next is young health screening benefit
nathan which is equal to 0.2 of the sum
assured
that is 1000 pesos starting on the
second year and every year thereafter
until the 10th year
so
you adding map
from the health screening benefits 1 000
times 5 a total of 5 000 pesos because
we got the lowest some ash worth of 500
000 pesos
on top of that
we have the health supplement benefit
which is two percent of the sum assured
to be given for the next six months
after the first major claim
again
in first major claim of 500 000
starting that month
five hundred thousand ibb gainer
every month for the next six months
for a total of sixty thousand
so all in all
all those benefits
nasa forty six thousand three hundred
fifty pesos
every year forty six thousand three
hundred fifty pesos
okay i hope you were able to see the the
plano forty six thousand three hundred
fifty pesos for the next ten years
and converting it
so
five hundred
pesos so five thousand pesos so 565
even if mattapos declined you
10 years to pay
the 406 463 350
is still lower than
the five hundred sixty five thousand
sun critical illness
however aside from this benefit
waiver of premiums
plan up until the end of the paying
period
so we only need to pay 1009 pesos and 24
cents
for just 10 years
and disabilities
hospital confinement benefit
1000 per day for 1000 days
so 45 years from copyright
hospital confinement benefit only lasts
until the age of 75.
enough time for us to really maximize
the 1000 days if ever in a mccarran time
of hospital confinement
if this is an icu confinement
1000 becomes 2000 per day for the next
365 days
the amount is only 6
879.76 per year for the next 10 years
if we total all of that no
10 years nothing beneath
that's only 68
797 for a total of 1 million coverage
for hospital confinement because if we
do the math 1000 pesos times 1 000 days
is equal to 1 million pesos
1 million pesos only cost us
per year for the next 10 years
okay
to better appreciate
the benefits of the plan
i
totaled
all the
benefits that you can get from the plan
a major critical illness claim a
maximized nation
the current in a minor critical illness
claim
the gohan health screening benefit
young health supplement benefit plus
the maximization of hospital confinement
all in all the plan is willing to
provide us
4.19 million pesos
only to pay
every year for the next 10 years the
plan is based on
the client's gender or a and age
so at this
point in this example we have a female
30 years old
so if you are younger than 30 years old
the premium is much lesser
however if you are older than 30 years
old especially if you are a male
the premium goes
if you wish to get a premium estimate
for this plano either your lowest
possible yeah
or
up to the maximum paid an ib guy for a
single client
please try to get ahold in the details
below
nothing wrong to get an estimate at
least you know your options
okay
so in 4.19 millionaire let's say
10 years ago
mrs juan de la cruz
that happened 10 years to pay
390 long in total
the king
premiums
in exchange to a maximum of 4.19 million
until the age of 100.
let's say
it
[Music]
just imagine it's still higher the
benefit is higher than what she paid for
during her lifetime
when we get this fwd fight
it also has an option to be paid
you can choose to pay semi-annual for 28
quarterly for 1586.92
monthly 5152.45
if you wish lesser than this your pedi
panating
settle
you can opt to remove hospital
confinement benefit fed in a mind
however if i were in your shoes
and i'm showing a man there's nothing
wrong to get more benefits especially
illness
why would we
gamble on that possibility
benefit for just a fraction of the force
so
uh we're here to advise you naman
whenever we talk to our clients
we don't
easily just recommend the plan
because we have several rosters of
options for you to choose from as
mentioned in the first
part of our video
as low as 1799 a year long
no we also have set for health very
basic multi critical illness plan
we also have a one-time claim
with investment via set for life health
bundle
and if you really want to be that's a
gorista type of persona
illness
we feel secured we feel guaranteed
benefits until age 100 then fwd is the
right plan for you
so we also have here the cash values
embedded in the policy
cash values are there to
give you
cash
if you request that you end the policy
before the expiration
so there is an equivalent cash value
depending on the age
you wish to terminate the plan
however you cannot reinstate the policy
if you already received the cash value
for the cash value let's say
the maya data fwd vibrant however on the
fifth gear mejo quinta
one issue reduced paid up
ibiza
if we fail to continue paying for the
plan
the initial benefit will be reduced up
to such point
in london cash value
um
is that you can use your cash values to
get a loan from
for example
um
critical illness
so what others do
is that they get a loan from the policy
depending that's a year na
from the policy
and then
he or she is still covered
for the benefits of the plan
is to pay for the interest of the loan
from the plan
so that way
um
on how to settle the medical expenses
because
he or she can easily
pay the loan plus the
value
depending on the corona in a major claim
or well appetizing major claim
and then you must supplementary benefits
fwd
writer
value
depending on a major or major critical
illness
as your guide to how much you can
either
learn from the plan surrender the plan
or
reduce paid up or macaroni extended term
okay
to give you more idea about these
options you can easily approach your
financial planner for you to better
understand
all right
um as you can see with the cash value no
from the 11th year until the age of 79
unlike other critical illness plans
variable unit link policies
veto guaranteed
after the 10th year
and then let's say at the age of 75
decline
on cash value
she can get as much as 407 195 that she
can get when she
surrenders the plan
or
maximum
amount
from the plan
with a certain interest
eight percent young interest
okay
so this page now enumerates the 42 major
critical illnesses you've covered you're
covered for under fwd vibrant
um
cancer group and non-cancer group
remember you can claim 100 percent of
the sum assured for up to three times
for cancer group and another three times
for the non-cancer group
donsa cancer group nathan casama
may cancer in a stage one lung make
answer in a stage two make answering
stage 3 and above
so we may refer to the policy itself for
the full definition of
what late stage cancer is
all right
so
major critical illness on both left and
right parts of an organ will be
considered as one critical illness claim
so let's see
organ
[Music]
illness claim because of what
happened to the left part of that organ
another critical illness this time
around the right part of the organ he
disha considered a second major critical
illness claim because that's considered
as one organ
left and right
i hope that was clear no so anub left
and
[Applause]
so for the major organ failure it you
[Music]
anemia liver disease lung disease
pancreatitis crohn's disease
fulminant viral hepatitis loss of
hearing loss of sight
major organ and bone marrow transplant
medullary cystic disease progressive
scleroderma
renal failure terminal illness also
ulcerative colitis
and we also have the heart and blood
vessels the non-cancer group and
cardiomyopathy
coron coronary artery disease myocardial
infarction heart bulb surgery primary
pulmonary arterial hypertension surgery
to aorta
we also have neuromuscular related
genome alzheimer's
appellate syndrome benign brain tumor
cerebral aneurysm requiring surgery
comatose for whatever reason basako
masha
loss of independent existence
motor neuron disease
multiple sclerosis muscular dystrophy
dystrophy
paralysis parkinson's disease and events
one cannot claim twice for the same
illness
for the same non-cancer illness so let's
say alzheimer's disease
this year a coronation of alzheimer's
hinisha considered another claim because
non-cancer however
the pug stroke or heart attack you
adding non-cancer critical illness
you can claim up to three times
so you know foundation not indito
and for the other critical illness the
non-cancer related we have here
bacterial meningitis encephalitis hiv or
age due to blood transfusion loss of
flames loss of speech major burns
is a vehicular accident and it was
considered a major burn you can claim
from this plan
major head trauma with severe brain
damage
occupationally acquired hiv
hiv or aids and severe rheumatoid
arthritis
so
when you get any of these critical
illnesses
tapos your cancer nathan up to three
times and then your heart attack stroke
up to three times into your conditions
that you can
claim against the policy
no subsequent major critical illness
benefits will be paid if you have
already received a benefit due to
terminal illness or loss of independent
existing in existence so let's say in a
current time and terminal illness
meaning to say
tina's
whatever is the subsequent major illness
after being diagnosed of a terminal
illness
benefit from the plan
and then
loss of independent existence
after being diagnosed of that because
when we say loss of independent
existence
or we cannot
[Music]
move from another place to another place
we cannot
take care of ourselves
on our own
conditions
subsequent critical major critical
illness
if you get all other things here you can
get as much as six times clean
so we also cover minor illnesses
you can claim once and get 25 of the sum
assured maximum of 1 million and you're
still be covered with our set for help
here
we can only cover maximum of 500 000 for
minoruno and fwd vibrant
our was able to
increase the maximum minor critical
illness benefit up to one million pesos
of double assets for health so anobi
and other invasive treatments for
coronary artery disease
diabetic retinopathy
early stage cancer you know stage 0 or
carcinoma in situ loss of one limb loss
of one lung removal of one kidney severe
osteoporosis surgical removal of
pituitary tumor are considered minor
critical illness
apart from that we also have juvenile
minor critical illnesses human minor
illnesses a specific language
because as you may know fwd vibrant can
also be availed by children as young as
15 days old
so let's say in the quran selena minor
juvenile illnesses or diseases
hemophilia a and b
insulin insulin dependent diabetes
kawasaki disease osteogenesis genesis
imperfecta type 3 severe asthma
systematic juvenile idiopathic arthritis
of the some assured up to 1 million
pesos maximum
until their age of 100.
we still expressed our love to them
because
even
[Music]
until 100.
so just to be transparent as well we
will lay down here the things that we
don't cover
fwd keeps its exclusions to a few
because we want you to celebrate living
more so most containers in exclusion
snap
here's a summary of the few things that
we do not cover in this plan you can
check the finer details in the fwd
vibrant critical illness policy contract
so base plan ensure pro
we will not pay any debt benefit if the
claim arises from suicide or
self-inflicted act by the insured while
seeing within two years
so walang death benefit claim
death is because of swiss suicide within
two years upon policy effectivity
however if suicide happened after the
second year
it may claim
from the plan
second we will not pay
any major or minor critical illness
benefit if the claim arises from the
list of the exclusions below
the insured committed any illegal or
unlawful act or failure to act
as much as possible don't get involved
with any illegal or
unlawful act like for example before
thai nakara
we were abusing drugs
oh or we were
proven to be very alcoholic
or we committed a crime that led us to
um
disabilities
another is
[Music]
loss of independent existence due to
psychedelic psychiatric related causes
so we need to type animal claims and
pre-existing conditions so it's very
very important that you reveal
or divulge to your financial planner any
of your pre-existing condition
cases
we're not that strict when it comes to
approving those with pre-existing
conditions so it's better that you
divulge it
subsequent illnesses due to your
pre-existing condition
you will not be at fault for
not having a plane because they
declaring an ammonium in your existing
condition
lastly we will not pay any major or
minor critical illness benefit if the
insured first experience a signs of a
condition within 90 days after the
effective date of the policy so as much
as possible
hindi taya makara
critical illness claimed within 90 days
a first signs of the condition within 90
days upon policy effectivity
all right all right
so
a supplementary plan rider in a man
uh your hospital confinement and the
benefit we will not pay any hospital
income benefit if the claim arises from
the list of exclusions below
same as
a base plan
the current iron and deliberate
self-inflicted act catholic addiction or
alcoholism
and
we will not pay any
hospital income benefit if they insured
first experience as signs of a condition
within 30 days after the effective date
of the policy so here in this plan
hospital benefit may take advantage not
in 30 days after
hayao makarov policy effectivity
okay
uh hospital benefit claim after three
days
that's why it's very important
but
you don't have to wait because we will
never know
[Music]
all right
canceling this policy if you find this
plan not suitable for your needs you can
cancel within 15 days from the date
that's been delivered to you so my
chance for
just send us a written request upon
cancellation we will return all your
paid premiums for this policy no
interest will be paid on the refunded
amount
if a claim is payable for this policy
before we receive your request for
cancellation we will pay you the claim
amount instead of the refund so let's
say
you're not claiming plan on
um what a accidental disability
you know
must obtain
benefit
rather than the refund definitely the
the benefit is higher than the refund so
that's the the policy for the
cancellation
last is
the last page that is acknowledgement by
the owner by the way
proposal
usually is presented to you digitally
you will receive an email or it will be
presented by an ipad
um
signature nino will be reflected here
digitally
so ana basin has happened on page nato
i acknowledge by signing below
i signify that i have carefully read and
understood the disclosures and
information contained in the sales
illustration and that my financial
wealth planner
then alleged proposal has fully
explained to my complete satisfaction
the principal features and benefits of
this plan so like what i did not explain
that then you know from start to finish
on benefits and plan
this sales illustration is valid for
three months
from the date it was prepared
any alteration shall invalidate this
sales illustration
ensure that she is already capable of
signing another signature for the policy
insured and of course the date
it
all right so i hope that the video
provides you better appreciation of our
newest and most comprehensive
most complete
critical illness plan only from fwd
until age 100
so whether or not we get sick
may benefit
from the plan whether or not we get
critically ill
from the plan
and it will be my privilege to
um give you
options
for for the plan to secure our future
eventually
so
just a few notes before we end the video
fwd vibrant you can have this for a
minimum some assured
basis
for the claims
five hundred thousand
and if you really want to get this plan
once and for all
your critical illness plan until age 100
cover yourself for as much as 20 million
pesos per claim
future critical
in 15 million
you can really spend it for whatever
reason
on critical illness insurance is not
like hmo
na um
insurance company
is your actual expense london hospital
union disadvantage
less insurance you are given cash
you are given cash
and it's up to you how to use it
is that you can get it
if you are only 15 days old no for your
kids
again very very dependent because the
gender in age of the insured
up to 65 years old
success 60 years old
you can also get this plan for
five year installment and ten year
installment
so five or ten maganda at least one
cache is a budget and
and of course the coverage is until
age 100.